In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to learn how to pronounce the UH as in BUTTER vowel.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将学习如何发音 BUTTER 中的 UH 元音。
This is a very relaxed sound.
这是一个非常放松的声音。
You can see UH.
你可以看到 UH。
The jaw drops, but the rest of the mouth remains very neutral.
下巴下垂，但嘴的其他部分保持非常中立。
UH.
UH。
The tongue is relaxed.
舌头是放松的。
The back presses down just a little bit, and the tip is forward.
舌头的后部稍微向下压，尖端向前。
UH.
UH。
Keep your face really relaxed.
保持你的脸非常放松。
Let's look at this sound up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个声音。
A very relaxed jaw drop with relaxed lips.
非常放松的下巴下垂，嘴唇放松。
The tongue presses down just a bit in the back.
舌头的后部稍微向下压。
Here's the word STUFF.
这是单词 STUFF。
Again, everything looks nice and relaxed.
再次，一切看起来都很放松。
The tongue presses down just a bit in the back.
舌头的后部稍微向下压。
In a stressed syllable, the vowel curves up, then down.
在重读音节中，元音先上升，然后下降。
STUFF.
STUFF。
UH.
UH。
In an unstressed syllable, it's lower and flatter in pitch, and a little quieter and quicker.
在非重读音节中，音调更低更平，声音更轻更快。
UH.
UH。
The vowel is unstressed in the word UNDO.
在单词 UNDO 中，元音是非重读的。
UH.
UH。
Let's take a look at this word up close and in slow motion.
让我们近距离慢动作观察这个单词。
Easy jaw drop.
轻松的下巴下垂。
Lips and cheeks remain very relaxed.
嘴唇和脸颊保持非常放松。
Tongue presses down slightly in the back.
舌头的后部稍微向下压。
Compare the stressed vowel above with the unstressed vowel below.
比较上面的重读元音和下面的非重读元音。
Notice, the jaw may drop a bit more for a stressed syllable.
注意，对于重读音节，下巴可能会稍微多下垂一点。
This is typical.
这是典型的。
Unstressed vowels and diphthongs are shorter, so there isn't as much time to make the full mouth position.
非重读元音和双元音较短，因此没有足够的时间来完成整个口腔位置。
The UH vowel, stressed.
UH 元音，重读。
STUFF.
STUFF。
UH.
UH。
The UH vowel, unstressed.
UH 元音，非重读。
UNDO.
UNDO。
UH.
UH。
Example words.
示例单词。
Repeat with me.
跟我重复。
Sometimes.
UH.
UH。
Sometimes.
Money.
UH.
UH。
Money.
Above.
UH.
UH。
Above.
Untie.
UH.
UH。
Untie.
Uphill.
UH.
UH。
Uphill.
Fun.
UH.
UH。
Fun.
Fun。